# Andrei Zvonkov

DRUPAL DEVELOPER



Senior Front-End Drupal Developer specializing in helping companies with **Design**, **Development**, **Usability** and **Accessibility** of their Digital Products and Services.

In the past 10 years, I have worked with companies such as Pfizer, Fox, 911 Memorial. I've been responsible for the creation, implementation and successful launch of numerous digital projects.

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- Drupal, Custom Theming, TWIG, Config, Views, Paragraphs, Layout Builder
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, ReactJs (GatsbyJS, NextJS)
- Component-based Theming, Atomic Design (Patternlab, Storybook)
- UX/UI, Design Strategy, Brand Identity
- Prototyping, Wireframing, IA (Figma, Sketch, InVision)
- Web Accessibility (WCAG 2.0)
- Agile development methodologies (Scrum, JIRA, Confluence)

### **WORK EXAMPLES**

Example: <u>lullabot.com</u> - Lullabot site redesign - <u>Prototype</u> (Next.js)

Role: Front-End Developer, UX/UI Designer Responsibilities: UX/UI Design, React, Next.js

Example: workbc.ca - Employment Services - Province of British Columbia - Drupal site redesign

Role: Front-End Developer

Responsibilities: Drupal Theming, Site Building, Config, CSS, JS, TWIG

Example: <u>home.sophos.com</u> – Sophos Home Cybersecurity redesign

Role: Front-End Developer, UX Designer

Responsibilities: UX/UI Design, CSS, JS, TWIG

Example: wdw.utoronto.ca - University of Toronto - Woodsworth College

Role: Front-End Developer, UX Designer

Responsibilities: UX/UI Design, CSS, JS, HTML

Example: <u>cheesebar.ca</u> – Agropur Dairy Cooperative

Role: UX Designer, Front-End Developer

Responsibilities: UX/UI Design, CSS, JS, HTML

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Freelance FE Developer / UX Designer	(2021- Present)
FosterInteractive - Front-End Dev / UX Designer	(2018 – 2021)
Appnovation – Front-End Dev	(2013 – 2018)
Digital Echidna - Front-End Dev	(2009 – 2013)
Rtraction - Front-End Dev, Designer	(2007 - 2009)

## **EDUCATION**

B.S. – Interactive Design and Multimedia (Andrews University)

